Hi I'm Amelia and I'm going to show you how to use a hot hair styling brush to curl your hair.
These are great because what they do is they bring a brush and a blow dryer and put it into one unit.
So it's a lot easier for you to use at home.
Basically what you are going to do is make sure you've got some styling product on your hair, your hair is not necessarily have to be completely wet, it can just be slightly damp like the model.
You want to turn it on, and really let it heat up, and you see how I'm twisting it the same way that your designer would in the salon.
Except they would be using a brush and a drier.
So you only use one hand instead of two.
And you really want that strand to heat up and dry.
You can also put it on low if you feel like that gives you a little bit more control.
And remove it off of the hot hair dryer and there you've got your curl.
You can continue to do this around your head and this will give you a great volume and body without having to use a brush and a blow dryer at the same time.
And this is how you use your hot hair curl dryer.